#### **Deivison Alves Justiniano**

### Personal declaration

Single, non-smoker, 40 years old, with 20 years of experience in vertical activities in which I developed my professional career. I have a degree in Private Security Management.

Initially working with mountaineering in Brazil, I migrated to rope access and nowadays I work as a Blade Repair Technician.

#### Personal information

**Date of birth:** 06/21/1984 Gender: Male Nationality: Brazilian

**Contact details** 

deivisonaj@gmail.com

+351 969821138

in LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/deivison-justiniano-48953422/

IRATA ID: 3/74229 WINDA ID: DA056797BR IPAF ID: 1719256 EU Driving Licence ID: L-2415364 6

Address: Calçada da Rinchoa, 13, 4º Dto. 2635-311 - Rio De Mouro, Portugal

### **Education and training**

Jorge Lozano - Trabalhos em Altura, Lda jorgelozano.pt

In progress GWO Enhanced First Aid In progress **GWO Advanced Rescue Training** 

alimaktraining.com **Alimak Group** 

19/07/2024 Operation of Service Lift model Dolphin & Beluga

Operation of Service Lift model Shark L 03/06/2024

**Vestas Energy Solutions** vestas.com/en

22/05/2024 Basic Turbine Operation MK11, V112 and EnVentus, Level D

LOTO level 2 16/05/2024

15/05/2024 Electrical Safety for Qualified Electrical Persons

vertline.pt/ Vertline (Portugal)

05/12/2022 - 10/12/2022IRATA Level 3 recertification

onrope.pt/ OnRope Unipessoal Lda (Portugal)

 $\overline{18/11/2022} - 18/11/2022$ GWO - Sea Survival 01/07/2022 - 01/07/2022NF C18-510 / B0 29/06/2022 - 29/06/2022 GWO - Lift User 06/06/2022 - 11/06/2022GWO - Full BTT

ANARA Wind SL (Spain) anaraformacion.com 30/04/2024 - 02/05/2024GWO - Full BST recertification

09/09/2022 - 18/09/2022GWO – Blade Repair

**IESMIG Technical College (Brazil)** iesmig.com/tecnico

06/07/2020 - 11/07/2022Work Safety Technician

www.controleacima.com/ Controle Acima - Training and Advice (Brazil)

23/04/2022 - 24/04/2022 Vertical Technical Rescue.

www.anhanguera.com/home/ **Anhanguera Educational College (Brazil)** 

16/01/2006 - 01/04/2009 Bachelor's degree on Personal and Property Security Management

## Work experience

23/05/2023 – current period Blade Repair Technician

Alpha Offshore Service A/S, (Denmark)

Responsible for repairing blades at Vestas - Denmark

23/02/2023 - 26/05/2023 Blade Repair Technician

Muehlhan Wind Service A/S, (Denmark)

Responsible for blade repair at Vestas - Scandinavia

27/06/2022 – 10/11/2022 Blade Repair Technician

OnRope Unipessoal Lda (Portugal)

Responsible for repairing blades at Nordex – France

15/04/2020 – 30/04/2022 Work at height technician

Tecniquitel - Society of Technical Equipment, S.A. (Portugal)

Technician responsible for preparing the training center for IRATA, GWO certifications and other training for access to structures, confined spaces and pre-hospital care. Occupation distributed in internal work at the Training Center and external work with clients, such as the Sines Oil Refinery and Águas do Tejo Atlântico.

01/07/2019 – 10/04/2020 Work at height technician

Jorge Lozano - Works at Height, Lda. (Portugal)

Slope containment and Installation of dynamic barriers, anchor points and lifelines.

# Language skills

Native Language: Brazilian Portuguese

Other language: American English Listening: B1 – Independent user

**Reading:** B1 – Independent user **Spoken Interaction:** B2 – Independent user

**Spoken Production:** B2 – Independent user **Writing:** B1 – Independent user

# Management and leadership skills

With extensive experience in training, leadership of work teams and rescue at heights, I trained several teams for access to structures, rope access and coordinated the Emergency Brigade at the Cambambe and Laúca hydroelectric plants in Angola. During this period, I had the opportunity to train and work with Portuguese firefighters and paramedics in rescue situations at heights, confined spaces and remote areas; These activities give me versatility in the field.

I have been developing my activities in Europe since 2019. I had the opportunity to prepare Tecniquitel's training center in an IRATA and GWO accredited training center.

In 2022 I had worked on repairing wind turbine blades for Nordex in France and I'm currently working on Vestas projects in Scandinavia.